<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>non-fiction on Best Books To Read</title>
    <link>https://bestbookstoread.info/tags/non-fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in non-fiction on Best Books To Read</description>
    <image>
      <title>Best Books To Read</title>
      <url>https://bestbookstoread.info/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://bestbookstoread.info/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 17:06:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bestbookstoread.info/tags/non-fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Science Books for Curious Minds</title>
      <link>https://bestbookstoread.info/posts/best-science-books-for-curious-minds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 17:06:05 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestbookstoread.info/posts/best-science-books-for-curious-minds/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re someone who loves exploring the mysteries of the universe and understanding how things work, then you&amp;rsquo;ll definitely enjoy these five science books that are perfect for curious minds like yours!
A Brief History of Time by Stephen Hawking, a classic that explores the origins and evolution of the universe, from the Big Bang to black holes. Written in a way that&amp;rsquo;s accessible to non-scientists, this book is a must-read for anyone who wants to understand the fundamental laws that govern the cosmos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Non-Fiction Books to Inspire and Enlighten You</title>
      <link>https://bestbookstoread.info/posts/best-non-fiction-books-to-inspire-and-enlighten-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:21:29 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bestbookstoread.info/posts/best-non-fiction-books-to-inspire-and-enlighten-you/</guid>
      <description>Looking for some non-fiction books to broaden your perspectives and inspire you? Check out these five must-reads:
Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind by Yuval Noah Harari, a fascinating exploration of how humans evolved and the impact we have had on the world around us. This book will challenge the way you think about history and the future.
The Power of Now by Eckhart Tolle, a spiritual guide to living in the present moment and finding inner peace.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
